Breaking Boundaries: The Science of Our Planet is a
documentary film directed by Jonathan Clay.
David Attenborough and scientist Johan Rockström examine Earth's
biodiversity collapse and how this crisis can still be averted.
Self - Narrator, played by David Attenborough.
Self, played by Johan Rockström.
Self, played by Elena Bennett.
Self, played by Jason Box.
Self, played by Terry Hughes.
Self, played by Maria Neira.
Breaking Boundaries: The Science of Our Planet is a 2021 documentary film directed by
Jon Clay, and presented by David Attenborough and Johan Rockström.
The film explores themes of pollution, scientific
study, coral reef, wilderness, interview.